Mexico
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Mexico
2.1.1.1.15
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1198
- Mexico, 2.1.1.1.15
  - Railroad station, San Antonio Texas, 13; 13207; M214; 4x5 (Box 1198)
  - Crossing the Rio Grande into Mexico, 1911; 14; 13201; M208; 4x5 (Box 1198)
  - Statue in Plaza de la Independencia, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 15; 13031; M32; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Fountain, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 16; 13032; M33; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Aqueduct, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 17; 13034; M35; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Cathedral, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 18; 13035; M36; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - View from Maximilian tomb through doorway, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 19; 13036; M37; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Maximilian tomb, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 20; 13037; M38; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - View from Maximilian tomb, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 21; 13038; M39; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Maximilian’s coffin in glass case, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 22; 13039; M40; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Interior of Maximilian’s tomb, Frank R. Roberson in foreground, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 23; 13040; M41; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Doorway of house, looking through into patio, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 24; 13125; M126; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Mexican street musicians, Queretaro, 1911 May 6; 25; 13177; M184; 4x5 (Box 1198)
  - Man and goat, Queretaro, 1911; 26; 13214; M281; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Plowing with oxen, Queretaro, 1911; 27; 13214; M327; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Post office, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 28; 13055; M56; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Y.M.C.A., Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 29; 13056; M57; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Hat market, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 30; 13063; M64; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Hat market, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 31; 13064; M65; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Cathedral, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 32; 13070; M71; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Chapultepec from bullring, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 33; 13095; M96; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Crowd at bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 34; 13103; M104; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Entering the ring, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 35; 13104; M105; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Procession entering the ring, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 36; 13105; M106; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Crowd at bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 37; 13106; M107; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 38; 13215; M217; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 39; 13215; M219; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 40; 13215; M221; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 41; 13215; M223; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 42; 13215; M224; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 43; 13215; M225; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 44; 13215; M226; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 45; 13215; M227; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 46; 13215; M228; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 47; 13215; M229; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 48; 13215; M230; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 49; 13215; M232; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 50; 13215; M234; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 51; 13215; M235; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 52; 13215; M236; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Bull fight, Mexico City, 1911 May 7; 53; 13215; M238; 4x5 film (Box 1198)
  - Residence of President Diaz’s son-in-law, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 54; 13041; M42; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Theater, building nine years, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 55; 13050; M51; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - American Legation, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 56; 13058; M59; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Clock presented by Turkey, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 57; 13062; M63; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Geranium detail, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 58; 13065; M66; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Bougainvillea, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 59; 13069; M70; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Home of President Diaz, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 60; 13072; M73; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Exterior of American Consulate, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 61; 13082; M83; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Old fountain used for 300 years, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 62; 13087; M88; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Petunias and fountain, Alameda Park, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 63; 13089; M90; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Garden around Bath of Montezuma, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 64; 13091; M92; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Old church, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 65; 13092; M93; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  - Sunset over Chapultepec, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 66; 13094; M95; 5x7 (Box 1198)
  Box 1199
- Mexico, 2.1.1.1.15
  - Chapultepec from north, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 1; 13100; M101; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Exterior of bullring, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 2; 13102; M103; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 3; 13107; M108; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Gateway and house, Calle de Liverpool, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 4; 13118; M119; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Main statuary group, Juarez Memorial, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 5; 13120; M121; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Juarez Memorial, detail of lion, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 6; 13121; M122; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Juarez Memorial on Avenida Juarez, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 7; 13122; M123; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Juarez Memorial through trees, Alameda Park, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 8; 13123; M124; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Aztec statue, Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 9; 13133; M134; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Calle de Cinco de Mayo looking toward cathedral, Mexico City, 1911 May 8; 10; 13146; M147; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Tile house, Jockey Club, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 11; 13057; M58; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Billboards in front of theater, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 12; 13071; M72; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 13; 13073; M74; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Peace monument, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 14; 13076; M77; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Groups at base of peace monument, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 15; 13077; M78; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Old church entrance, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 16; 13079; M80; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Imperial restaurant, light blue and white, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 17; 13081; M82; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Statue of Charles IV, Plaza de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 18; 13084; M85; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - House of Dr. Limantour, Plaza de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 19; 13085; M86; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Castle of Chapultepec from Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 20; 13093; M94; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Chapultepec, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 21; 13096; M97; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Chapultepec, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 22; 13097; M98; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Chapultepec under arch of trees, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 23; 13099; M100; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Avenida Juarez looking north, showing Alameda Park on left, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 24; 13108; M109; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Paseo looking north, buildings on right, Alameda Park on left, Mexico City, 1911 May 9; 25; 13109; M110; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Mrs. Delutom’s hacienda, Diaz’s daughter, Hacienda Guadalupe, 1911 May 10; 26; 13023; M24; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Typical overseer on horse in front of pulque plant, Frank R. Roberson standing next to horse, Hacienda Guadalupe, 1911 May 10; 27; 13024; M25; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Frank R. Roberson on horse in front of pulque plant, overseer next to horse, Hacienda Guadalupe, 1911 May 10; 28; 13025; M26; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - House of Cortez, Coyoacán, 1911 May 10; 29; 13042; M43; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - House of Alvarado, 1911 May 10; 30; 13043; M44; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Church on battleground of Churubusco, 1911 May 10; 31; 13044; M45; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Country club near Mexico City, 1911 May 10; 32; 13053; M54; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Entrance drive to hacienda, Mexico City, 1911 May 10; 33; 13074; M75; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Old church, Coyoacán, 1911 May 10; 34; 13078; M79; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Cattle, mountains in background, outskirts of Mexico City, 1911 May 10; 35; 13080; M81; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Aqueduct fountain, 1571, by Chapultepec, Mexico City, 1911 May 10; 36; 13101; M102; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Tree of 18 deserters, Battle of Churubusco, 1911 May 10; 37; 13111; M112; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Garden, San Ángel, 1911 May 10; 38; 13112; M113; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - The Inn at San Ángel, Frank R. Roberson and party seated in foreground, 1911 May 10; 39; 13113; M114; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Garden at inn, San Ángel, 1911 May 10; 40; 13114; M115; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Granary of hacienda, 1911 May 10; 41; 13127; M128; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Granary, 1911 May 10; 42; 13128; M129; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Market under trees, Xochimilco, 1911 May 10; 43; 13129; M130; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Among the floating gardens, Xochimilco, 1911 May; 44; 13216; M291; 4x5 film (Box 1199)
  - Among the floating gardens, Xochimilco, 1911 May; 45; 13216; M304; 4x5 film (Box 1199)
  - Hacienda homes of paeons, 1911 May 10; 46; 13135; M136; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Hacienda entrance, 1911 May 10; 47; 13136; M137; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Hacienda barnyard, etc, 1911 May 10; 48; 13137; M138; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Hacienda building, 1911 May 10; 49; 13138; M139; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  - Hacienda, paeons quarters, 1911 May 10; 50; 13139; M140; 5x7 (Box 1199)
  Box 1200
- Mexico, 2.1.1.1.15
  - Frank R. Roberson in automobile train in doorway of hacienda granary, 1911 May 10; 1; 13140; M141; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Looking down from Pyramid of the Moon, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 2; 13000; M1; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 3; 13001; M2; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Original walls of Sun Pyramid, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 4; 13002; M3; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - View from top of Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 5; 13003; M4; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Moon looking up sacred street, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 6; 13004; M5; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 7; 13005; M6; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party looking over valley from Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 8; 13006; M7; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 9; 13007; M8; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Moon, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 10; 13008; M9; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson climbing steps up Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 11; 13009; M10; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 12; 13010; M11; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 13; 13011; M12; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party sitting on steps ascending Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 14; 13012; M13; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramid of the Sun viewed from Pyramid of the Moon, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 15; 13013; M14; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Small mounds or pyramids between Pyramids of the Sun and the Moon, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 16; 13014; M15; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Steps, old and new, ascending pyramids, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 17; 13015; M16; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Side of pyramid showing projecting stones, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 18; 13016; M17; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party on steps leading up Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 19; 13017; M18; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramids, distant view, pulque in foreground, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 20; 13018; M19; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Pyramids, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 21; 13019; M20; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Ruins of houses from pyramid, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 22; 13020; M21; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Excavation at foot of pyramid, Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 23; 13022; M23; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Interior of museum, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 24; 13045; M46; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Toltec skulls in museum, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911 May 11; 25; 13124; M125; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Native guides on top of Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 26; 13162; M169; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson standing near portion of original wall at base of Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 27; 13163; M170; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party ascending the Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 28; 13164; M171; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party climbing the Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 29; 13165; M172; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party sitting on steps up the side of the Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 30; 13166; M173; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and guide in excavated passage into Pyramid of the Moon, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 31; 13167; M174; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party on the way to the pyramids, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 32; 13200; M207; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Sentry at entrance to grounds around pyramids, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 33; 13202; M209; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson by old gateway near Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 34; 13203; M210; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Mexican guide on top of Pyramid of the Sun, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 35; 13204; M211; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Flock of sheep and cattle, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 36; 13206; M213; 4x5 (Box 1200)
  - Shipping barrels of pulque to Mexico City, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 37; 13213; M242; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party returning from pyramids in hand cars, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 38; 13213; M247; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson bargaining for souvenirs, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 39; 13213; M260; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Drinking sweet pulque, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 40; 13213; M262; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Frank R. Roberson bargaining for souvenirs, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 41; 13213; M263; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Man with skin full of pulque, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 42; 13213; M278; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Drinking sweet pulque, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 43; 13213; M309; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Typical horsemen, San Juan Teotihuacán, 1911; 44; 13216; M254; 4x5 film (Box 1200)
  - Church of the Well, Guadalupe, 1911 May 12; 45; 13026; M27; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Church of the Well, Guadalupe, 1911 May 12; 46; 13027; M28; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Spanish cemetery, Guadalupe, 1911 May 12; 47; 13028; M29; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Stone stairs leading to summit of Tepeyac Hill, Guadalupe, 1911 May 12; 48; 13029; M30; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - The Collegiate Church, Guadalupe, 1911 May 12; 49; 13030; M31; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Liberty Bell on National Palace, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 50; 13047; M48; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - National Palace, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 51; 13048; M49; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Cross on house and street scene, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 52; 13054; M55; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Old American cemetery, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 53; 13060; M61; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Monument to American soldiers, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 54; 13075; M76; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Circular bed on Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 55; 13110; M111; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Planting and walk on sides of Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 56; 13116; M117; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Interior of Tree of the Dismal Night, Popotla, near Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 57; 13126; M127; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Bas relief on Aztec statue, Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 58; 13132; M133; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Aztec statue, Paseo de la Reforma, Mexico City, 1911 May 12; 59; 13134; M135; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - R. G. Dun and Company, general office, Mexico City, 1911 May 13; 60; 13061; M62; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  - Mr. Saner of R.G. Dun and Company, Mexico City, 1911 May 13; 61; 13141; M142; 5x7 (Box 1200)
  Box 1201
- Mexico, 2.1.1.1.15
  - Mutual Life Insurance building, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 1; 13046; M47; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Façade of theater, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 2; 13049; M50; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Façade, new theater, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 3; 13051; M52; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Façade of new theater, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 4; 13052; M53; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Methodist Book Concern, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 5; 13059; M60; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - San Juan de Letrán and San Francisco, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 6; 13142; M143; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Calle de Capuchinas, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 7; 13143; M144; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Calle de San Francisco, Mexico City, 1911 May 15; 8; 13144; M145; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Spanish dagger [yucca plant], 1911; 9; 13115; M116; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Frank R. Roberson and soldier on horseback, 1911; 10; 13145; M146; 5x7 (Box 1201)
  - Cadets at drill, military college, Chapultepec, Mexico City, 1911; 11; 13149; M150; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Prisoners guarded by soldiers, Mexico City, 1911 May; 12; 13150; M154; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Prisoners handcuffed to soldiers, Mexico City, 1911 May; 13; 13151; M156; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Cadets drilling, Chapultepec, 1911; 14; 13152; M157; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Cadets at drill, military college, Chapultepec, 1911; 15; 13153; M158; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Cadets at drill, military college, Chapultepec, 1911; 16; 13154; M159; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Soldiers on road, Chapultepec, 1911; 17; 13211; M267; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Sunset behind mountains between Nuevo Laredo and Monterrey, 1911; 18; 13156; M163; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Looking into valley from train, between Esperanza and Malata, 1911; 19; 13155; M162; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Town of Malata from railroad, between Esperanza and Malata, 1911; 20; 13157; M164; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Looking at Malata from railroad, between Esperanza and Malata, 1911; 21; 13158; M165; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Malata valley from railroad between Malata and Esperanza, 1911; 22; 13159; M166; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Mountains and valley from railroad train, between Esperanza and Malata, 1911; 23; 13160; M167; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Looking over valley from railroad, between Esperanza and Malata, 1911; 24; 13161; M168; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Railroad train, between Esperanza and Malata, 1911; 25; 13197; M204; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Natives at station, Maltrata, 1911; 26; 13182; M189; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Flower sellers, Maltrata, 1911; 27; 13214; M275; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower sellers, Maltrata, 1911; 28; 13214; M329; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Selling fruit at railway station, Maltrata, between Mexico City and Vera Cruz, 1911; 29; 13176; M183; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Leaving for Vera Cruz, Buena Vista Station, Mexico City, 1911; 30; 13168; M175; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Pottery store, Mexico City, 1911; 31; 13169; M176; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Public wash house, Mexico City, 1911; 32; 13171; M178; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Native huts, 1911; 33; 13172; M179; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Cloth market, Mexico City, 1911; 34; 13173; M180; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Umbrellas over merchandise, cloth market, Mexico City, 1911; 35; 13174; M181; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - “Restaurant” on city street, Mexico City, 1911; 36; 13175; M182; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Woman and child, Mexico City, 1911; 37; 13178; M185; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Pulque shop, Mexico City, 1911; 38; 13179; M186; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Street scene, Mexico City, 1911; 39; 13180; M187; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Street markets, Mexico City, 1911; 40; 13181; M188; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Native market, Mexico City, 1911; 41; 13183; M190; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Cloth market, Mexico city, 1911; 42; 13184; M191; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Children, Mexico City, 1911; 43; 13185; M192; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Group under trees, 1911; 44; 13189; M196; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Old market, Mexico City, 1911; 45; 13190; M197; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Donkeys loaded with baled hay on road to Cayeran, 1911; 46; 13191; M198; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Donkeys loaded with vegetables, Paseo de la Viga, Mexico City, 1911; 47; 13192; M199; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Boy on loaded donkey, on road to Churubusco, 1911; 48; 13193; M200; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Boy on donkey, 1911; 49; 13194; M201; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 50; 13211; M241; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 51; 13211; M245; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 52; 13211; M246; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Street booths, Mexico City, 1911; 53; 13211; M248; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Hat market, Mexico City, 1911; 54; 13211; M249; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Common market, Mexico City, 1911; 55; 13211; M250; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Public letter writers, Mexico City, 1911; 56; 13211; M251; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 57; 13211; M255; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Entrance to Thieves Market, Mexico City, 1911; 58; 13211; M257; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 59; 13211; M258; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Common markets, Mexico City, 1911; 60; 13211; M259; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Public letter writers, Mexico City, 1911; 61; 13211; M261; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 62; 13211; M264; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Native huts, Mexico City, 1911; 63; 13211; M268; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Common markets, Mexico City, 1911; 64; 13211; M276; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Common market, Mexico City, 1911; 65; 13211; M277; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 66; 13211; M279; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Native huts, Mexico City, 1911; 67; 13211; M280; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Flower market, Mexico City, 1911; 68; 13211; M308; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Public letter writers, Mexico City, 1911; 69; 13211; M310; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Woman with baby on back, Mexico City, 1911; 70; 13211; M314; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Woman with baby on back, Mexico City, 1911; 71; 13211; M319; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Native huts, Mexico City, 1911; 72; 13211; M320; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Street sweeper, Mexico City, 1911; 73; 13211; M322; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Guards at entrance to National Palace, Mexico City, 1911; 74; 13211; M323; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party in automobile, Mexico City, 1911; 75; 13211; M325; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Native huts, Mexico City, 1911; 76; 13211; M330; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Urchin in streets, Mexico City, 1911; 77; 13212; M256; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Goats and cattle by roadside near Mexico City, 1911; 78; 13212; M265; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Woman washing clothes by roadside near Mexico City, 1911; 79; 13212; M269; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Goats and cattle by roadside near Mexico City, 1911; 80; 13212; M302; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Hat market, Mexico City, 1911; 81; 13216; M239; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Street scene, Mexico City, 1911; 82; 13216; M252; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Public letter writers, Mexico City, 1911; 83; 13216; M253; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  - Train entering cut on railroad between Mexico City and Vera Cruz, 1911; 84; 13195; M202; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Train rounding curve between Mexico City and Vera Cruz, 1911; 85; 13196; M203; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - End of Canal Nacional, Mexico City, 1911; 86; 13208; M215; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Canal Nacional, Mexico City, 1911; 87; 13209; M216; 4x5 (Box 1201)
  - Horseman by Canal Nacional, Mexico City, 1911; 88; 13212; M312; 4x5 film (Box 1201)
  Box 1202
- Mexico, 2.1.1.1.15
  - Candle shop outside of church, Guadalupe, 1911; 1; 13170; M177; 4x5 (Box 1202)
  - Children coming out of church, Guadalupe, 1911; 2; 13186; M193; 4x5 (Box 1202)
  - Venders of cakes and water near the Chapel of the Well, Guadalupe, 1911; 3; 13187; M194; 4x5 (Box 1202)
  - Street venders of tortillas, Guadalupe, 1911; 4; 13188; M195; 4x5 (Box 1202)
  - Beggars, Guadalupe, 1911; 5; 13212; M243; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Beggars, Guadalupe, 1911; 6; 13212; M244; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Stone mast and sails, Guadalupe, 1911; 7; 13212; M287; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Trolley car, Córdoba, 1911; 8; 13214; M272; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Rurales (mounted police), Córdoba, 1911; 9; 13214; M274; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Rurales, Córdoba, 1911; 10; 13214; M326; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Rurales, mounted police, Orizaba, 1911; 11; 13216; M328; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - Frank R. Roberson and pulque plant, near Mexico City, 1911; 12; 13212; M283; 4x5 film (Box 1202)
  - First class railway coach, Frank R. Roberson at window, 1911; 13; 13198; M205; 4x5 (Box 1202)
  - Natives by railroad train, 1911; 14; 13199; M206; 4x5 (Box 1202)